你们开始录像了要告诉我
Just tell me when you're rolling.
我们开始录像了
We're rolling.
有很多人...
A lot of people...
FLYco作品
都质疑这故事的真实性
have questioned what really happened.
这部小说出版以后
And when the novel was first published,
越来越多的质疑
it didn't take long
接踵而至
for there to be even more questions asked.
很多问题至今依旧是个谜
It's always remained a mystery.
很感谢你能来
And that's why I wanted to thank you
为我们解答这些疑惑
for coming in to meet with us.
让我们了解更多的真相
To help shed some light on the events.
不客气
Okay.
他把这本书献给了你
He dedicated the book to you.
你能告诉我们书中
Can you tell us how much of his novel
有多少事件是真实发生的吗?
was based on fact?
全部都是真的
All of it.
事情发生在1969年...
It was 1969...
能告诉我们那年夏天发生了什么吗?
What can you tell us about that summer?
佛罗里达州 护城河县
什么? 你刚刚问的什么?
Question? What was the question?
对于1969年那个夏天你记得些什么?
What do you remember about that summer 1969?
那年真的很热 真的真的很热
It was hot. It was real hot.
上帝肯定也热得汗流浃背了 实在是太热了
God must have been sweatin', it was so hot.
我们想知道谋杀的事
Tell me about the murder.
1969年12月12日
我想问一下 我说这些你们付我多少钱?
Hey, how much, how much I'm gettin' paid for this?
是的 卡尔警长就是个肮脏 恶心的恶魔
Well, Sheriff Call was this evil, nasty,
简直无恶不作
disgusting son of a gun.
黑人都痛恨他
Black people hated Sheriff Call
因为在他的两个任期内
because he killed so many of us
我们无数的同胞死在他手里
during his two terms in service.
其中也包括我的家人
Some of my family was included.
白人也一样很惧怕他
White people feared him too.
有人对他实在忍无可忍 于是把他做掉了
So somebody got fed up with his fat ass, and killed him.
这就是那年夏天发生的事
That's what happened that summer.
报童
护城河县欢迎白佬和黑鬼
传说他在死前
They say he dragged his intestines
拖着内脏走了一英里
for a mile before he died.
那些脑残的白人还立像纪念他
Crazy white people even built a statue for him.
那你是怎么和
How did it come about
詹森一家人扯上关系的?
that you worked for the Jansens?
他们的妈妈离家出走以后
I was cleaning for them part time,
我兼职做起了他们家的保洁阿姨
right when his mamma ran off.
然后沃德和我 沃德是哥哥
And Ward and I, Ward was his brother,
他那时还在读高中
he was in high school at the time
我们两个一起照顾他
and we raised him together.
小杰克那时候才五岁
Little Jackie was five at the time.
那他的父亲呢?
Where was his father?
老詹森那时候
W.W. was just
在追一个姑娘 你懂的
chasing girls, you know.
而且还在办一份当地的报纸
And running the local newspaper.
叫做护城河县论坛报
The Moat County Tribune.
沃德他好吗?
How's Ward?
挺好的 就是很忙
He's good, he's good. Real busy.
沃德是一个作家...
Ward was a writer...
为迈阿密时报工作
uh... for the Miami Times.
他常常写一些关于...
He used to write about, uh...
其实那时候他还是小有名气的
well, he was kind of famous, you know,
因为他写的都是关于民权运动的文章
'cause he wrote about the Civil Rights Movement
为穷人和不公正事件打抱不平
and the poor and the unjustly accused.
所以后来夏洛特女士
That's how come that lady Charlotte
才会写信给他
started writing letters to him.
然后发生了这样那样的事
Stuff like that.
是的
Yeah.
再后来杰克 像我说的一样 他是一个游泳运动员
And then Jack, like I said, he was a swimmer.
而且...
And, uh...
他游得很好 几乎是专业水准 但是
almost professional, very close but then
他还是被游泳队开除了
he got kicked off the swim team,
他还被大学开除了
he got kicked out of college,
他只能回到家 在爸爸的报社当报童
and he came back home to his papa's house to deliver newspapers.
他是很不愿意回家的
He didn't want to come back home,
但是除了家他无处可去
but he didn't have nowhere else to go.
杰克 你的音乐太大声了
Jack, you better turn that music down.
你知道老詹森 看到你这样会抓狂的
You know W. W. gon' be mad at you.
去他的 安妮塔 下次进来你能敲下门不?
Dang it, Anita, can you please knock?
我说不定在里面打飞机呢
I could've been jerking off in here.
算了吧 你有啥我没见过呀
Please, it ain't nothing I ain't seen before.
你在干什么呢?
What are you doing?
我在把你的东西捡起来 我天天做的都是这活儿
I'm picking up your stuff, like I do every day.
哦别这样 今天休息一天吧 外面实在太热了
Oh come on, not today. It's too hot for that.
我帮你吧
I'm just helping.
你不是在帮我 别帮倒忙了行不
You're not helping me. You don't have to help me.
别闹了
Come on.
下床来我要铺床了
Get off the bed so I can make it.
给我来点羽衣甘蓝吧
Go fix me some collard greens.
这是我的床
It's my bed.
我知道这是你的床 然后呢?
I know it's your bed. Really?
就因为这是你的床 那你倒是给我好好理理呀
Because it's your bed, you should fucking make it.
他们取消了史莫瑟兄弟的演唱
They cancelled "The Smothers Brothers."
哦 不 那可是你的最爱呀
Oh, no, that's your show.
是的 我喜欢那节目 我喜欢迪克和汤米两兄弟
Well, I love that show. I love Dick and I love Tommy.
- 快躺下 我来体验体验你的工作  - 哦 是的 就这样 给我找点麻烦
- Lay down. Let me be you for a second.  - Oh, yeah, right. Get me in trouble.
你想要做我的工作 那我变成你? 好吧
You want to be me, I get to be you? Okay.
- 好的 我会爱上这工作的  - 杰克 我能进来吗?
- Okay, I'll love this.  - Jack, may I come in?
- 哦 好的 太好了  - 出去 快出去 到外面去
- Oh, good, okay.  - Go away, go out. Go back out.
好吧 那我现在开始打飞机吧 好的
Okay. I better start jerking off first. Okay.
杰克 很抱歉打扰了你的欢乐时光
Jack, sorry to interrupt your masturbation,
但是我现在要理床了呀!
but I'm here to clean the bed!
- 我在打飞机呢!  - 我要把这一团糟都理干净啊!
- I could've been jerking off!  - I'm gonna clean everything!
我在打飞机啊!
I could have been jerking off!
滚出去! 别来烦我!
Get out! Clean my shit up!
我们现在所得到的回报
Get all that we have received in return,
只不过是政治操纵的
is just another smooth exercise
- 另一种柔和形式而已  - 这女孩真不错
- in political manipulation.  - Good girl.
欺骗与欺诈问题
Deceit and deception,
对于我们个人问题的麻木与漠视
callousness and indifference to our individual problems,
还有那些政客们玩的龌龊伎俩
and the disgusting playing of divisive politics,
让年轻人与老年人对立
pitting the young against the old,
让劳工与管理层对立 南北对立
labor against management, north against south.
你有事找我吗?
Did you want to see me?
你这礼拜找沃德谈过了吗?
Have you spoken to Ward this week?
- 还没有  - 你好 杰克
- No.  - Hello, Jack.
他没告诉你让你来这儿吗?
He didn't mention anything to you about coming here?
我不敢相信 你爸爸竟然要我报道这东西
I can't believe your father's making me report on this.
我的意思是 看看她
I mean, look at her.
向我们开放
to open our society.
她准备竞选下届总统
She plans to run for president next.
他们想和希拉里・范・维特聊一聊
They want to talk to Hillary Van Wetter.
你可别被普利策奖糊弄了
Don't you let that Pulitzer Prize fool you.
他还啥都不知道呢
He don't know everything yet.
没理由来这里
Ain't no reason to come up here
跟那混蛋扯在一起 准没好事
stirring up shit with that asshole.
我只想说认识到这点
I just wanted to say that it is very important
对于每个美国人来说都很重要...
for all Americans to recognize...
夏洛特・布莱斯喜欢危险的男人
Charlotte Bless loved her some dangerous men.
于是她给监狱里的人写信
She wrote men in prison.
最后她终于爱上了其中一个
She finally fell in love with one.
她决定要把他保释出来
She was determined to get him out.
为什么你们这儿连冰块都没有?
Why y'all ain't got no ice in here?
你想要冰块的话 回你自己家呗
You want ice, go to your house.
夏洛特
Charlotte.
- 哦 这是我最爱的节目  - 你觉得怎么样 夏洛特?
- Oh, that's my show.  - What you think, Charlotte?
我不怎么喜欢 再弄蓬松点
I don't like it. Make it looser.
你还在跟那个监狱里的\佬通信吗?
That's that nigger you've been writing?
不 这回是个白人
No. This is my white man.
哦
Ohhh.
昨天发生了什么? 我好像错过了什么好事
What happened yesterday? I missed it.
听着这句 他觉得 我就是他的天使
Listen to this. He thinks I'm his angel.
- 他的天使?  - 嘘嘘嘘 闭嘴听下去
- His angel?  - Shhh. Shut your face.
- 这货今年几岁啦?  - 哦 我的天哪
- Bitch, how old is he?  - Oh, my God.
- 这个老东西对你很中意啊  - "如果人世间真的有天使存在的话
- He's a fine motherfucker that's trying to fuck you.  - "Ever there was an angel in the world,
那一定是你 我的天使
my angel, it must be you,
但是没有天使会愿意做 我希望你做的事
but no angel would do the things I dream that you want."
你是天使 他的天使
Your angel, his angel.
- 嗯  - 写得真好
- Mm-hm.  - That's hot.
他说 "如果你真的存在 那我就去信教去"
He say, "If you truly exist, I may become a religious man."
啊哈!
Ah!
"穷尽一生 我的心只想找一个港湾"
"All my life, my heart has tried to find a place
我想是叫做... 家的地方"
I cannot name... a home."
你最好给你自己找个年轻点的
You need to find yourself a young one.
那样他才能满足你
He'll fuck you real good.
- 他说我是他的家  - 恩恩
- He says I'm his home.  - Hm.
从在监狱里服刑的
Got a hundred different men
一百个男人中挑选出的一个
writing her from the penitentiary.
这就是她的男人
That's her man.
哦 不 这才是我男人
Oh, no. This is my man.
这就是我缘定今生的人
This here's the one.
呵呵
Mm-hm.
沃德回到家去调查
Ward came home to investigate
希拉里・范・维特的罪行
the conviction of Hillary Van Wetter.
当地人对这事都很排斥
The town wasn't too happy about it
- 而且他的爸爸也不支持这样做  - 哦 算了吧
- and neither was his papa.  - Oh, shit. Ugh.
沃德...
Ward...
有匹马在停车位里
there's a horse in the parking lot.
我们就骑着它回家吧 亚德利
It's our ride home, Yardley.
额 人们都到哪儿去了?
Uh, where is everybody?
今天是周日
It's Sunday.
人们要么在家 要么在做礼拜
People's either at home or at church.
真不走运
It's a shithole.
嘿 兄弟
Hey, man.
嘿 是你呀
Hey, you.
最近还好吗?
How you doing?
- 杰克 这是我朋友亚德利・阿奇曼  - 你好
- Jack, meet Yardley Acheman.  - Hey.
- 这是我弟弟 杰克  - 游泳健将 对吗?
- My little brother, Jack.  - The swimmer, right?
- 是的 他现在是我们的司机哦  - 好的 太好了
- Yeah, he's our driver now.  - Right, good.
上车吧 我来拿行李
Here, let me get these.
- 那是我的打字机  - 你越长越壮了
- That's my typewriter.  - You've gotten big, boy.
打字机可得轻拿轻放哦
Just be careful with the typewriter.
还是那么有精神呢 是因为常游泳吗?
Got all pumped up. Is that from swimming?
现在不游了
Not anymore.
错了! 错了! 不对呀!
No! No! No!
亚德利很爱惜他的西服哦
Yardley's real particular about his suits
- 还有他的打字机  - 是的呢 它很贵哦
- and his typewriter.  - Well, it's very expensive.
谢谢你
Yes. Thank you.
我怎么坐进去?
How do I get in?
当心头 别磕到了
Watch your head. Watch your head.
- 别碰我的头  - 告诉他你是哪里人 亚德利
- Don't touch my head.  - Tell him where you're from, Yardley.
我是从伦敦来的
London.
原来如此!
Ah!
我从纽约... 来这儿的时候
When I came here... from New York,
我来这儿应聘这份工作...
I was interviewing for the job...
我在纽约做的是广告方面的工作
and I was in advertising in New York,
我指出 这里的广告业和纽约的不太一样
and I mentioned that it was simply different in New York.
那是什么驱使你从纽约市
So how'd you get from New York City
来到后来的大都市 佛罗里达的呢?
to the metropolis of Lately, Florida?
詹森宅邸
Jansen residence.
所以我一路南下而且应聘了报社的工作
So I came down South and I interviewed at the paper.
詹森先生 罗伯塔小姐打电话找你
W.W., Miss Roberta's on the phone.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
- 我们不接电话  - 安妮塔...
- We don't take phone calls.  - Anita...
- 谁是罗伯塔小姐?  - 我们不接电话 安妮塔
- Who's Miss Roberta?  - No calls, Anita.
你是从伦敦哪一个地区来的 亚德利?
What part of London you from, Yardley?
额 伦敦我都很熟
Um, all over London.
- 这里有好一点的干洗店吗?  - 你是说?
- Is there a good dry cleaning here?  - Excuse me?
干洗店
Dry cleaning.
- 干洗店?  - 是的
- Dry cleaning?  - Yes.
- 你吃的差不多了 是吗?  - 是的
- You ain't gonna eat that, are you?  - Uh-uh.
你不吃饭怎么能赢得游泳比赛呢?
How you gonna win those swimming meets if you don't eat?
我已经退役了
I'm retired.
退役了 杰克 你还没累到要退役吧
Retired. Jack, you ain't even tired enough to be retired.
你们工作具体是干什么的?
How is it exactly you guys work?
比如报道 某个男孩因入会仪式而溺死
I mean, like that boy drowned at his initiation?
是这样 亚德利是一名作家...
Well, Yardley's the writer...
沃德可以说是 负责搜集素材的
And I'd guess you'd say Ward is the nuts and bolts.
是的 当我还是记者的时候
Yeah. When I was a reporter,
我们会请改稿员通过电话把故事记录下来
we had rewrite men who took the stories over the phone.
不 不 不 我不是改稿员
No, no, no. I'm not a rewrite man.
我就是作家
I'm the writer.
我就是要把事实呈现在公众面前
I'm the one who puts the facts into perspective.
哦!
Oh!
是的 现在时代不同了 詹森先生
Yes. It's a different world now, Mr. Jansen.
显而易见
Clearly.
今时不同往日了呢
Times have changed a bit, sir.
"迈阿密时报"到底
What interest does "The Miami Times"
对希拉里・范・维特有什么兴趣呢?
have in Hillary Van Wetter?
他在狱中杀人了吗?
He murdered somebody in jail?
即使他是个罪犯...
Even if he was guilty...
- 但显而易见 他被处以私刑...  - 他也是有人权的
- It was a lynching, pure and simple.  - he had certain rights.
而且就算他是有罪之人
And even if he was guilty...
希拉里还是享有不容忽视的权利的
Hillary has rights that the process completely disregarded.
这就是我们此行的原因
And that's why we're here.
很抱歉 各位 但是我真的得走了
I'm very sorry, everybody, but I'm going to have to leave.
抱歉 亲爱的
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
我明天一大早还得去做评估呢
I have early evaluations first thing in the morning.
- 靠近点 亲爱的  - 我真的很抱歉
- Come here, sugar.  - I apologize.
那就到这儿吧
All right, buddy.
沃德?
Ward?
晚安了 孩子们
Good night, boys.
沃德?
Ward?
看来他没意识到自己的肤色问题
Seems mighty sure of himself for a colored.
沃德说他们需要一个司机
Ward said they need a driver.
一个司机?
A driver?
你在外面到底是干什么的?
What you do out there?
你在迈阿密交新朋友了吗?
So you meet anybody new out there in Miami?
是有那么几个
I met a few.
- 哦  - 那里各种各样的人都有 你知道的?
- Oh, yeah.  - All types down there, you know?
你要离那些凶巴巴的人远一点
You stay away from those rough ones.
还记得上次发生的事情吗
Remember what happened the last time.
你的孩子们现在怎么样?
How your kids?
你看起来还是很漂亮 宝贝
You look beautiful, babe.
他们过的不错 日子过的很舒坦
They're doing good. They're doing really good.
我今晚下班以后
As soon as I get out of here,
回去看看他们 然后再给他们做一顿晚饭
I'll go see them and make dinner all over again.
你啥时候也一起来吃饭吧
You should come to that dinner, too.
我会去吃晚饭的呢
I'll come to that dinner.
我想你走的时候...
I think Ellen is maybe number four...
艾伦才四岁吧
since you left.
嗯
Yeah.
所以不能把这帮小崽子当回事
That's why I don't take them bitches too seriously.
他们来来去去 来来去去的
They come and they go and they come and they go.
知道吧?
You know what I mean?
- 还行吗 亚德?  - 唉哟
- How you doing there, Yard?  - Oh, jeez.
嘿 小伙 把门关上啊
Hey, close that door, boy.
省得你爸又要吵吵
I don't want your daddy screaming about all the flies
苍蝇都放进屋了
getting in the house.
呵
Hmm.
那谁啊 杰克?
Who is that, Jack?
呃...
Uh...
我想去詹森先生的办公室
I'm looking for the office of Mr. Jansen.
"迈阿密时报"的沃德・詹森
Ward Jansen of "The Miami Times."
- 我问你她是谁?  - 我就在这家报社工作
- I said who is it?  - I work for the Times.
- 是吗?  - 嗯
- You do?  - Yeah.
啊
Huh.
- 嗯 我叫夏洛特・布莱斯  - 我叫杰克・詹森
- Well, I'm Charlotte Bless.  - I'm Jack Jansen.
- 啊 我帮你拿吧  - 哦
- Here, let me get that.  - Oh.
- 嗨  - 都是文件
- Hey.  - All my files.
他办公室在车库
The office is in the garage.
你这位记者 还真年轻
You look a little young to be a journalist.
- 其实我只是司机啦  - 啊
- I'm really just the driver.  - Oh.
不过我也动笔的
But I do write.
我也是啊 我会写信 写得还不错
So do I. I write letters. I'm pretty good.
嘿 伙计们!
Hey, guys!
这位是夏洛特・布莱斯小姐
This here is Miss Charlotte Bless.
啊 目前还是小姐身份
Oh, not for long.
不过 我和希拉里已经订婚了
Hillary and I are engaged to be married.
你好 布莱斯小姐 我叫沃德
Hello, Miss Bless. I'm Ward.
哦 沃德先生 可算见到您了
Oh, Mr. Ward, good to finally meet you.
- 你信里没提订婚的事儿啊  - 先洗洗吧
- You didn't mention the engagement in your letters.  - Go clean yourself up.
呃 没多久的事儿 他才跟我求的婚
Well, it only just happened. He just proposed.
- 哦 怎么这么脏  - 嗯 怎么搞的?
- Oh, that looks nasty.  - Well, how did I do that?
等一下
Excuse me a second.
- 我去给布莱斯小姐拿点喝的  - 我是亚德利・阿奇曼
- Get Miss Bless something to drink.  - I'm Yardley Acheman.
我们以为你跟希拉里没见过面
We thought you and Hillary hadn't met.
呃 只看过照片
Well, only in pictures,
不过我们这几个月一直通信
but we been writing each other for months
彼此都很了解
and we understand ourselves just perfect.
沃德 她的文件放哪儿呢?
Ward, where should I put her files?
你们需要了解的
Everything you need to know about Van Wetter
关于维特的文件案底
that's been in the papers,
都在箱子里
is here in these boxes.
你要感兴趣的话
Our exciting correspondence is in that box.
还有我跟他之间的密信
In case you're interested.
放到我桌上吧 小伙
My desk, Jackie boy.
詹森先生 真的我本来只想来感谢你的
Mr. Jansen, I really just wanted to thank you.
谢谢你回我的信
I wanted to thank you for returning my letters.
谢谢你愿意帮我 让希拉里离开那烂地方
And for helping me get Hillary out of that hellhole.
嗯 现在还不能让你预订蜜月啊
Well, I wouldn't go booking the honeymoon just yet.
但我们会想办法
But we are going to fight his sentence
为他翻案
and the way it came about.
谢谢 太感谢了
Thank you. Thank you so much.
没人该受死刑 布莱斯小姐
Nobody deserves the death penalty, Miss Bless.
希拉里・范・维特也一样
Not even Hillary Van Wetter.
呃 抱歉 啊 所有东西我都按字母顺序排好了
Um, excuse me. So, everything is ordered alphabetically.
我说过 呃... 你叫什么?
I was telling, um... what's your name?
- 亚德利  - 哦 亚德利
- Yardley.  - Yardley.
呃 所有文件
Um, that all of the files,
所有案底资料
um, everything that's been in the papers,
- 都在最上面的纸盒里  - 这些东西很有用
- is in the top box.  - This is gonna be a great help.
他是无辜的 你们会明白的
He's an innocent man. You're gonna find that out.
他坐的是冤狱
Wrongly convicted.
这些对我们来说是个很好的开始
This is gonna get us off to a great start.
- 我做了大量调查  - 看得出
- I've done a lot of research.  - I see that.
这会儿 你是不是先修修妆?
In the meantime, you need to freshen up or anything?
- 杰克 带布莱斯小姐去洗手间  - 不 我就待这儿吧
- Jack, show Miss Bless to the washroom.  - No, I think I'll just stay here.
有些问题可能还得跟你说下
You might have some questions that you need answered.
在这儿我也能修妆
I can freshen up just here.
给我来点凉啤酒 杰克
Cold beer for me, Jack.
你真招人爱 杰克
You're adorable, Jack.
要有的话 给我来杯冰茶
I will take an iced tea if you have it.
- 你要点什么 沃德?  - 我不用
- You want anything, Ward?  - I'm good.
你们会发现 呃...
You'll see, uh...
箱子里的文件数量非常庞大
it's an enormous amount of work what's with the boxes.
我不知道在这儿干嘛 这些箱子干嘛的?
I don't know what to do here. What's with the boxes?
呃 我们得从这些箱子开始
Well, we're gonna start on it.
杰克他爱上了夏洛特・布莱斯
My Jack was in love with Charlotte Bless.
这淫娃 瞅人第一眼
I could tell that horny little boy
就想把人压倒在身下
wanted to jump her on first sight.
谁也搞不清 她怎么会跟希拉里・范・维特订婚
Everybody was confused why she was engaged to Hillary Van Wetter.
龌蹉 这白人下流胚烦着呢
Nasty, white trash swamp.
"给我写信的那些杀人犯
"All the killers who have written me,
他们只会想着舌抵玉户
want to press their mouths into my vagina,
顶烂我的屁股
and some, even the crack of my behind,
可希拉里・范・维特不这样
except Hillary Van Wetter.
他没这淫念
He has no such desire.
他想别人给他做口活
He wants to be sucked off himself.
我想这种心理证明了他的清白"
I consider this psychological proof of his innocence."
她可真够淫邪
She is one nasty little nut job.
咱是不是太拿她当回事了
Think we've been taking her a little too seriously.
你这么快就耐不住了
You sure get bored quick.
不 我可不想在这佛罗里达的破地方
No. Can tell I'm not going to get laid anytime soon
搞点风流韵事 所以...
in this Floridian shit pit, so...
- 听着...  - 嘿 凯西 是我
- Listen...  - Hey, Kathy, it's me.
希拉里跟她说 警方声称在他屋里
Hillary tells her that the knife
- 我是亚德利啊  - ...找到的刀子
- Yardley.  - ...and the bloodied shirt,
沾血的衬衫
that the deputies claim to have found in his house,
在开庭审理前都不翼而飞了
somehow got lost before the trial.
嗯 我也想你
Yeah, I miss you, too.
什么?
What?
你好 凯西
Hello, Kathy.
布莱斯小姐想去监狱外面看看
Miss Bless wanted to look at the prison.
杰克的第一个任务就是送她过去
Jack's first assignment was to take her there.
我猜他知道我在这儿
I bet he knows I'm here.
呐 两个人如果以非常方式...
See, people who fall in love outside...
陷入爱河
of a normal relationship,
他们会有感应...　心灵感应
they have these powers... telepathic powers.
希拉里和我有那种感应 你懂得?
Hillary and I have that kind of connection, you dig?
你为啥不在大学念书呢?
Now why ain't you in college?
啊?
Huh?
啊 我上学那会儿是练游泳的
Uh, I was a swimmer when I was in school.
- 真假?  - 是哦
- No kidding?  - Yeah.
- 我也是练游泳的  - 是吗?
- I was a swimmer.  - You were?
当然 要不是我这该死的卷发
Uh-huh. I'd swim like a mermaid,
我一定是游泳健将
if it wasn't for my damn curly hair.
给我授课的都是直发
I think straight hair gives me class.
好吧
All right.
不错
Good.
那?
So?
呃 有天晚上我们喝醉了 然后... 嗯...
Well, we was drunk one night, and, uh...
我...
I just...
我闹脾气 就...
I lost my temper and just...
呃 就把池子给放空了
well, I emptied the pool.
大学吗?
At your college?
佛罗里达大学
The University of Florida.
我想他们把这视作故意毁坏
They called that vandalism, I guess.
做这事可不是听上去那么简单
It's actually not as easy to do as it sounds.
那你经常闹脾气了?
So you lose your temper often?
嗯
Mm.
这地方每个小伙都和你一样
This place is full of boys just like you,
在某一天 闹脾气了
who lost their temper one day.
离他这么近 真有点饥渴难耐
I'm getting horny being this close to him.
哦 宝贝
Oh, baby.
他估计也是欲火中烧
I bet he's horny for me all the time.
是
Yeah.
嗯
Mmm.
哦 我能感觉到他
Oh, I can feel him.
要帮忙吗两位?
Can I help you folks?
哦 没
Oh, no.
是的 警官 呃... 嗯
Yes, Officer. Uh... hm.
我们只想在你的停车场待会儿
We just wanted to sit in your parking lot for a little while.
为嘛?
What for?
他爸关在这儿 我们给他传送点感应
His daddy's in there and we wanted to send him good vibrations.
传送啥?
Some good what?
哦 那种特别的心灵感应
Oh, these special things called good vibrations.
对不起 女士 你们不能在这儿停车
Sorry, ma'am. Y'all can't park here.
哦
Oh.
好的 警官
Yes, Officer.
警方并未去证实
The story that Hillary told the deputies
希拉里提及的细节
was never investigated.
这事他只在证人席说过
He simply told it once from the witness stand,
也没人让他详细陈述
and was never asked to elaborate,
包括他自己的律师
not even by his own lawyers.
- 很高兴再次见到你 沃德  - 很高兴见到您
- Good to see you again, Ward.  - Nice to see you.
先生 这是我的合作搭档 亚德利・阿奇曼先生
Sir, this is my writing partner, Mr. Yardley Acheman.
当然
Of course.
我想我们最好
I suppose the best place to start,
从头说起
would be the beginning.
我1897年出生在这座县城
I was born in this county.
我的父母人穷志不穷
1897, to poor but proud parents.
派恩先生 咱能省点时间
Mr. Pine, could we skip 65 years,
把这65年略过吗?
save everyone some time?
希拉里・范・维特1965年的案件?
Hillary Van Wetter, 1965?
哦 未经当事人的允许
Oh, I can't agree to talk to you about that matter.
我不能和你们讨论这件事
Not without my client's permission.
他也和大家一样 享有隐私权
He's entitled to his privacy, just like anybody else.
- 你们经过他的允许了  - 他给你写过信
- You have his permission.  - He wrote you.
我得查一下
I'll have to check that out.
我确信这些信就在你的案底里 派恩先生
I'm sure the letters would be in your files, Mr. Pine.
你是这么说 可我得保护我的当事人
That's what you say, but I have a client to protect.
这样
Look here.
如果我们非得找个律师
If we have to get a lawyer of our own down here
整理出这些案底 那么到时候
to sort this out, then while he's here,
我们就得让他彻底调查范・维特先生的案子
we're gonna have him look through every aspect of Mr. Van Wetter's case.
包括他的辩护能力
Including the competency of his defense.
希拉里・范・维特在法庭上的辩护没有任何问题
There was nothing wrong with the defense Hillary Van Wetter got in court!
那你就更没啥好顾虑的了
Then you have nothing to worry about from us.
我们只想和他谈谈
We just want to talk to him.
然后我们就离开你的...
Then we'll be out of your...
你根本不了解这个人!
You don't know a thing about this person!
你还嫩着点 小伙!
You've been in this world for five minutes, boy!
你不必这样 派恩先生
Now that's just not necessary, Mr. Pine.
是 这是我的办公室 我想怎么说就怎么说!
Yes. I talk the way I want in my office!
好吧 那您会安排我们见面的 是吧?
All right. Then you'll arrange the meeting, will you?
快点! 我们来不及了!
Quick! We're gonna be late!
你拿结婚证了?
You get the marriage license?
这真让人不敢相信!
I can't believe we're doing this!
操! 杰克 再去敲下门吧
Fuck! Jack, go knock on the door again.
她来了 喔 宝贝
There she is. Whoa, baby
- 呵 我说吧...  - 早上好 布莱斯小姐
- Well, I say...  - Good morning, Miss Bless.
看看黛西・梅
Look at Daisy Mae.
早啊
Morning.
你看上去真不错
You look just fine.
希望他喜欢
Hope he likes it.
呃...
Uh...
你能关下车窗吗?
Would you mind putting up the windows?
会吹乱头发的
It's gonna muss my hair.
你真假?
Are you serious?
我这一身汗 跟个怀孕的修女一样
I'm sweating like a pregnant nun back here.
难以置信!
Unbelievable!
嗨
Hi.
给你们15分钟
You got 15 minutes.
不准有任何肢体接触
No physical contact of any kind.
不准录音
No tape recorders.
不准向犯人传送物品
No object may be passed to the prisoner.
我就在门外
I'll be right outside this door.
范・维特先生
Mr. Van Wetter,
我叫沃德・詹森
my name is Ward Jansen.
- 这是我的搭档 亚德利・阿奇曼...  - 你看上去和照片里一样
- This is my associate, Yardley Acheman...  - You look like your picture.
嗯 是吗?
Mmm. I do?
谢谢
Thank you.
他们是你的报童?
These your paperboys?
嗯啊
Mm-hm.
他们会为我们做什么呢?
What they gonna do for us?
他们是来救你的
They gonna save you.
他们来救我们?
They're gonna save us?
嗯啊
Mm-hm.
操 他们连自己都救不了
Shit. They can't even save themselves.
范・维特先生 我们本想向你询问
Mr. Van Wetter, we wanted to ask you,
你的案件中丢失的证据
about the lost evidence in your case.
闭嘴 没看我忙着吗?
Shut up. Can't you see I'm busy?
你现在能为我做点什么吗?
Will you do something for me right now?
哦 哦 我也想
Oh. Oh, I wish I could.
把你的大腿分开点
Spread your legs open a little bit.
嗯 好
Mmm. Yeah.
撕开你的连裤袜
Now tear off them pantyhose.
扯掉
Rip those off.
好 嗯
Yeah. Mm-hm.
移开你的手 嗯
Move your hands away. Mmm.
好
Yeah.
张开你的嘴...
Now open up your mouth...
想象下 你在信中和我写的那些
you picture what you wrote me in your letters.
你个贱货!
You bitch!
哦 我爱你
Oh, I love you.
这怎么回事?
What the hell's going on in here?
- 你是个好女孩  - 我警告过你们! 探监结束了!
- You're a good girl.  - I warned y'all! This visit's over!
我告诉你们探监... 走了!
I told y'all this visit was... Come on!
来啊 希拉里 不!
Come on, Hillary. No!
不! 什么也没发生!
No! There's nothing going on!
操! 不!
Shit! No!
他妈的怎么了? 我没动那女孩!
What the fuck? I didn't touch that girl!
不! 不!
No! No!
你们他妈笑什么?
What the fuck you laughing about?
走吧 布莱斯小姐
Come on now, Miss Bless.
那之后杰克回家吐了一场
Jack came home and threw up after that.
他不能相信在看到那一幕后
He couldn't believe he still loved her,
他依然爱着她 可他确实爱她
after what he saw, but he did.
- 你是老詹森是孩子?  - 嗯
- You're Ward Ward's boy?  - Mm-hm.
护城河县最奇怪的父子
Most contrary man in all of Moat County.
今天我能为先生们做点什么呢?
What may I do for you gentlemen today?
关于卡尔警长的谋杀案
It's about the murder of Sheriff Call.
有些关于案件的
I understand that there's some physical evidence
重要证据丢失了?
relating to the case that was lost?
是 先生 我想是的
Yes, sir. I believe there was.
那我们想知道
Well, we was wondering what sort of explanation,
相关部门有什么解释呢
the department might have.
我不知道
I wish I knew.
范・维特先生曾切掉了副警长的大拇指
Mr. Van Wetter once cut a deputy's thumb off.
你们知道吗?
Did you know that?
我记得 那是因为一张罚单
It was over a traffic ticket, if I remember.
没有了拇指 有好多事你不能做
You can't do much without your thumb.
这是我们和灵长类动物的区别
It's what separates us from the primates.
就一件小事来说 你再也不能摸你老婆的乳头了
For a little thing like holding your wife's titty.
- 你没结婚吧 詹森先生?  - 没有
- You're not married, Mr. Jansen?  - No.
这样一件小事 你却不能做
A little thing like that, you can't do it.
或许我需要跟参与逮捕行动的
Maybe I'll just go talk to the deputies,
副警长谈谈
who was involved in the arrest.
你跟谁谈都行
You can talk to whoever you want,
只要他们都愿意和你谈 但没人愿意
as long as they'll talk to you. But they won't.
为什么?
And why is that?
因为他们没有忘记希拉里 对他们中的一员做的事
They haven't forgotten what Hillary did to one of their own.
法官承认一项
The judge allowed testimony,
他从没见过证据成立
based on evidence that he never even saw.
比起希拉里 他更相信警察的话
He took the officer's word over Hillary's.
这也不能怪他 大家都这么觉得
I can't say I blame him. Nobody does.
你打到我的脸了
You got me in the face there.
你会问
So you've got to ask him.
从2:00到6:00他在哪?
Where was he between 2:00 and 6:00?
我会问他关于他写的东西
I'm gonna ask him about some things he wrote,
那些写给夏洛特的信
some letters to Charlotte.
终于来了
Here we go.
稍等
Hold.
早上好 范・维特先生
Good morning, Mr. Van Wetter.
你怎么没穿裙子?
Where's your dress?
你不喜欢我这样吗?
You don't like me like this?
一个叫... 沃德
You know a prisoner by the name of...
沃德的囚犯
Ward, Ward, Ward.
你认识一个叫
You know a prisoner by the name
- 鲍勃・瓦伦丁先生的囚犯?  - 范・维特先生?
- of Mr. Bobby Valentine?  - Mr. Van Wetter?
德马库斯・威廉姆斯先生 鲍勃・希顿先生呢?
Mr. Demarcus Williams, Mr. Bobby Hinton?
另一个叫吉米・爱德华的囚犯
Another prisoner by the name of Jimmy Edwards,
还有一个德马库斯
another one, Demarcus.
还有 名字是库特吧 我记不清他的姓了
I think his name is Curt. I forgot his last name.
无所谓了 你知道这些人的共同点吗?
Anyway, you know what they all have in common?
嘿 马丁・路德・金
Hey, Martin Luther King.
- 你知道这些人的共同点吗?  - 什么?
- You know what they all had in common?  - What?
他们都穿裤子
They all wear pants.
这里所有的男人都穿裤子!
Every goddamned man in here wears pants!
你穿成这样跟他们有什么区别?
How am I supposed to tell you apart from them?
- 别那么跟她说话!  - 坐下 杰克
- Don't talk to her like that!  - Sit down, Jack.
快坐下
Sit the fuck down.
范・维特先生 我们时间不多 知道吗?
Mr. Van Wetter, we don't have a lot of time, all right?
我们要进行下一步了
We got to move on.
无论如何你都会进行下一步的 是吧 沃德?
You're gonna move on one way or another, Ward?
沃德是老大!
Ward's in charge!
他会按照他的方式进行... 行不通也不罢休
He's gonna get his way... till he don't.
也许脸上那道疤就是这么来的
Maybe that's how he got his scars on the face.
你在给布莱斯小姐的信中提到
You mentioned in one of your letters to Miss Bless
- 案发的时候...  - 转过身来 贱人!
- that you was working...  - Turn around, bitch!
- 你正为...  - 对 对
- At Uncle Tyree...  - Yeah, yeah,
泰利叔叔工作
at the time of the murder.
- 什么样的工作?  - 修剪草坪
- What kind of work you doing?  - Lawn work.
修剪草坪
Lawn work.
下次要么穿裙子来
You wear a dress in here next time,
要么你就别来了! 贱人 看着我!
or you don't bother coming! Bitch, look at me!
别再带那个自认为是
And stop bringing that fucking nigger,
穆罕穆德・阿里的黑鬼来了!
think he Muhammad Ali with you!
范・维特先生 过来坐
Mr. Van Wetter, come have a seat.
还以为自己是卡修斯・克莱 黑鬼
Cassius Clay, nigger.
给我们5分钟 我们让她换裙子来
We can get a dress here in five minutes.
过来坐下吧?
Why don't you have a seat?
回去吧 小子!
Go home, boy!
真不能理解...
I don't know...
夏洛特 你从哪弄来的那条裤子?
Charlotte, where does one get pants like that from anyway?
我觉得我们这案子要输啊
Well, I think we got the case licked.
就跟该死的马戏团一样!
This is a fucking circus!
在这个小镇
In this town,
威尔顿・派恩帮卡尔警长连任
Weldon Pine helped get Sheriff Call re-elected.
这间屋子里剑拔弩张
Tension was brewing in the house.
杰克因为希拉里和夏洛特的事吃醋
Jack was getting jealous of Hillary and Charlotte.
他还因为沃德和亚德利的关系吃醋
And he was getting jealous of Ward and Yardley, too.
沃德是个不轻易与人亲近的人
Ward wasn't somebody who attached himself to just anybody.
你爸爸的女朋友 叫什么名字?
Your dad's girlfriend, what's her name?
杰克不明白 为什么他和亚德利那么要好
Jack couldn't understand why he was so attached to that Yardley.
不 你没有
No, you didn't.
你经历的
What is the hottest temperature,
最高温度是多少?
that you've ever been in?
125华氏度
125.
你呢?
How about you?
把手伸出来 手都会融化的
Just put your hand out and it burns off,
我在佛罗里达的时候 那里最热 你呢?
The hottest was when I lived in Florida. How about you?
没注意 我从不注意温度
It doesn't bother me. I never pay attention to it.
潮湿和寒冷就像一把刀 穿透你的身体
Cold and wet just goes fucking through you like a knife
但... 无所谓了
but... I don't know.
那范・维特先生呢? 他是清白的吗?
So how's Mr. Van Wetter today? He still innocent?
不知道 如果他是...
I don't know. If he is...
就算他是 也不一定能证明
he sure as hell didn't have no help proving it,
至少叫威尔顿・派恩的人证明他不是清白的
not from that Weldon Pine guy anyway.
能给我个叉子之类的吗?
Could I have a fork or something?
鸡腿用手吃就可以了
The chicken legs, you eat those with your hands.
那是你们家的习惯
Maybe at your house.
这是南方 亲爱的
This is the South, sugar.
你们知道我的想法
Anyway, you know how I feel about that.
- 你用手吃土豆泥吗?  - 你真要...?
- Do you eat your mashed potatoes with your hands?  - Do you really want to...?
- 你真要... ? 你真的... ?  - 给我双筷子 安妮塔
- Do you really want to...? Do you really want to...?  - Bring me some chopsticks, Anita.
你真的认为
Do you really want to take the shot...
一个清白的男人或女人
on putting to death a man or a woman,
会被判死刑吗? 我是不会
when maybe they're innocent? I mean, I don't.
我无法那样生活
I don't want to try to have to live with that.
- 另外...  - 你到底是要吃它还是要折磨它?
- On the other hand...  - Are you gonna eat that or torture it?
跟你说了 我不饿
Told you, I'm not hungry.
那是因为你有爱情
That's 'cause you're in love.
我还知道你还在伺机而动
I know who you're sniffing around, too.
安妮塔 别在饭桌上逗他
Anita, please don't tease him at the table.
另外 如果某人是有罪的
On the other hand, if somebody's guilty,
你要为他们年复一年的生活报销吗?
well, you want to pay their room and board 365?
当然
Absolutely. Ah!
抱歉
I'm so sorry.
无所谓啦 只是冰茶而已 不会留下污渍的
Anyway, it's just iced tea. It ain't even gonna stain.
你会想 杰克应该交过女朋友了
You'da thought Jack woulda had a girlfriend by now,
但他只是看床下的黄色杂志
but all he did was jerk off to the pictures
打飞机
in those nudie magazines that was under his bed.
现在 她是他日夜思念的人
Now she was all he could think of night and day.
他绝对是陷入爱河了
Oh, yeah, he was definitely in love.
他要她
He needed her.
你看什么呢? 给我拿来
What you reading? You give it to me.
这是什么破玩意 "洛丽塔"
What is this shit? "Lolita."
色情的 肯定是
Porno, I bet.
你需要个女朋友
You need a girlfriend.
看看那群女孩
Look at them girls over there.
去认识一下 去吧
Go on and introduce yourself. Go on.
我在这就好
I'm just fine right here.
你想让我给你吹箫 是不?
You want me to blow you, don't you?
你不用回答 我知道的
You don't have to answer. I know it's true.
我不会因为一时痛快...
I'm not gonna blow a friendship...
而失去一个朋友
over a stupid little blowjob.
听懂了吗?
You hear me?
为什么和我说这些?
Look, why you talking to me like that?
看见那个穿蓝色泳衣的女孩没? 她会给你吹箫的
See that one in blue? She'll blow you.
我不想让她给我吹
I don't want someone like that blowing me.
你没进监狱真是个好事
It's a good thing you're not in prison,
因为在那你没的选
because you wouldn't have a choice there.
去你的
Fuck you.
杰克 回来嘛
Jack, come back here.
天啊 帕姆
Oh my God. Pam.
那是什么? 他还好吗?
What is that? Is he okay?
他是不是过敏了?
Is he having an allergic reaction?
被水母蜇了吧?
A jellyfish sting or something?
肯定是该死的水母
A fucking jellyfish did that.
应该对着水母蜇的伤口尿尿
You're supposed to piss on a jellyfish sting.
这也太尴尬了
We're gonna have to do something embarrassing.
- 你只能挺住了  - 嘿!
- You got to hang in there.  - Hey!
- 你要...  - 你要在他身上尿尿?
- Well, you're gonna...  - You'll piss on him?
你们要干什么?
What are you doing to him?
叫救护车
Call an ambulance.
- 他有过敏反应!  - 闭嘴吧你!
- He's having a reaction!  - Shut the fuck up!
- 别推我!  - 你应该尿...
- Don't push me!  - You're supposed to piss...
滚远点! 我能看见
Get the fuck out of here! I can see this.
我看出他中毒了 你不能尿...
I can see he's poisoned. You don't pee on...
- 别推我!  - 我扇你了啊
- Don't push me!  - I will slap your face.
- 滚一边去  - 好吧
- Get the fuck out of here.  - All right.
我会跟你算账的! 我要报警
I said, I will kick your ass! I'm going to call the police.
- 滚!  - 好吧
- Move it!  - Fine.
就算有人要对他尿尿 那个人也得是我!
If anyone's gonna piss on him, it's gonna be me!
去死吧你!
Fine, fuck you!
他不喜欢陌生人在他身上尿尿!
He don't like strangers peeing on him!
醒醒 醒醒
Come on. Come on.
醒醒 小子 起来了!
Come on, baby come on! Wake up!
醒醒! 靠!
Come on! Shit!
醒醒
Come on.
醒醒嘛!
Come on!
你不会有事的!
You're gonna be okay!
杰克啊
Jack.
你干嘛呢?
What are you doing here?
你觉得呢?
What do you think I'm doing here?
跟你说了进门之前
Told you to knock on my door
先敲门嘛
before you come in my room.
别说话
Oh, hush up.
我给你带了些东西
Here, I brought you something.
把药吃了
Take these pills.
我真难闻
I smell awful.
那是因为那个金发妞尿了你一脸
That's because that blond lady peed all over your face.
来 喝了它
Ugh. Here, drink this.
还疼吗?
Does it hurt?
我冷 我冷 冷
I'm cold, I'm cold, I'm cold.
好消息 杰克 我们上报纸了
Congratulations, Jack. We're in the paper.
"沙滩上争分夺秒抢救濒死男性
"Fast action saves lately man at beach.
亚巴马州的夏洛特・布莱斯
Miss Charlotte Bless of Mobile, Alabama"
在事故发生地
apparently saved Mr. Jansen's life
及时在詹森先生身上小便
by urinating over the areas of his body,
从而救了他的命"
where he was attacked."
"包括受伤者的胳膊 生殖器和脸"
"These included the victim's arms, genitals and face."
杰克 我并不知道
Jack, I had no idea.
我不知道你爸爸
I had no idea that your own father,
会把那样的事登上报纸
would print something like that.
美联社都登了
It made the AP wire.
你现在是全国知名了
You're famous all over the country.
"家有喜事" 好题目
"Home Remedy." Good title.
我爸想把我怎么样?
What's Dad trying to do to me?
这叫新闻效益 杰克
It's called the newspaper business, Jack.
真是的
Oh, shit.
放开他 杰克! 你会弄死他的
Let him go, Jack! You're gonna kill him.
杰克 放手
Jack, let him go.
你再碰我一下
You put your hands on me again,
- 我就干死你!  - 是吗?
- I will fuck you up!  - Yeah?
死去吧 黑鬼!
Fuck you, nigger!
他需要女人
He needs to get laid.
他需要一个狗链子
He needs a fucking straitjacket.
他性生活抑郁
He's sexually repressed.
40岁的女人才性抑郁呢
Sexually repressed is a 40-year-old woman,
监狱里的男人都能让她们兴奋!
who's obsessed with prison cock!
- 真难听  - 冷静点
- That's not nice.  - Calm down now.
去你的冷静!
No, fuck calm down!
我才不会让一个毛头小子叫我黑鬼
I'm not having some kid call me a nigger.
我现在就要他滚蛋!
I want him out of here now!
亚德利啊?
Yardley?
杰克 我们去监狱
Jack, let's go to the prison.
你们俩继续在这吵吧
You two can stay here and keep arguing.
这回我自己跟希拉里谈
This time I'm talking to Hillary by myself.
走吧
Come on.
他都不会看你一眼的
He's not even gonna look at you
除非我穿着漂亮的裙子去
if I'm not there in a pretty dress.
那他太可悲了
Well, that's too bad for him.
嘿沃德
Ward.
我们走着瞧
You'll see.
我知道杰克不是故意的
I knew Jack didn't mean to say it.
但那时候我们住在一起
But those were the times we were living in,
发生了就是发生了
and it was what it was.
亚德利这边呢 就...
Yardley, on the other hand, well...
法医报告上说警长
Forensic report says that the sheriff,
在凌晨2点到3点间被刺杀
was stabbed between 2 and 3 AM.
恩 就像我跟你说的
Yep. Like I told you,
当时我跟我的泰里叔叔在奥蒙德海滩
I was with... my Uncle Tyree doing lawn work,
修剪草坪
in Ormond Beach at the time.
- 修剪草坪?  - 对
- Lawn work?  - Yes, sir.
- 是指偷窃吗?  - 是
- You mean stealing?  - Yes, sir.
从高尔夫场地偷草皮
Stealing sod off a golf course.
一个开发商出钱要的
A developer paid through the teeth for that shit.
我们卖了草皮 我们直到日出前
We sold it and we didn't make it back,
才赶到河流那
to the river till sunrise.
- 什么样的开发商?  - 公寓楼的
- What kind of developers?  - Condominiums, man.
- 有名字吗?  - 没有
- You got a name?  - No, I don't.
副警长们说 他们在凌晨6点发现警长的尸体
Deputies say they found the sheriff's body at 6 AM...
但是他被杀的方式
but it was the way he was killed.
让所有人认为是你干的
That's what makes everybody assume it was you.
- 你怎么想?  - 你说呢
- What you think?  - You tell me.
我不是这里唯一一个身藏砍刀的人
I ain't the only one carrying a machete around here.
没错
True.
副警长们去了泰里的住处
The deputies went to Tyree's house,
他说他一晚上都在睡觉
he said he'd been sleeping in bed all night,
还有一家子人为他作证
and had a whole bunch of family members there to confirm it.
之后他们去了你的房子...
Then they go to your house...
找到了沾血的衬衫和刀
where they find the bloodstained shirt and knife.
是的 好吧 听我说
Yeah, all right. Listen to me.
我所有的刀和衬衫都沾了血
Every knife and shirt that I own is stained in blood.
这是我的谋生之道
It's what I do for a living.
我剥鳄鱼的皮
I'm gutting alligators for their skin.
行吗? 我是个单身汉
Okay? I was a bachelor.
没有人帮我洗衣服
I didn't have nobody to do my laundry.
大概有人帮你洗衣服
You probably got somebody to do your laundry.
你觉得呢?
What you think?
我确信你有
I bet you do.
鳄鱼的血绝不可能和警长匹配的 对吧?
They never matched the blood to the sheriff's, did they?
告诉我如何找到泰利
Tell me how to find Tyree.
仁慈的怀抱是如此的宽广
The arms of mercy are so wide,
他们会接受任何人
they will accept any man,
但他们不会接受穿裤子的人
but they will not accept any man wearing pants.
我的女人在哪儿?
Where is my woman?
Where's my woman?
现在你唯一需要对话的人就是我 孩子
The only one you need to talk to right now is me, baby.
我唯一需要对话的人?
The only one I need to talk to?
我是唯一一个 我就是你的仁慈
I'm the only one. I'm your mercy.
我是你宽大的臂膀 我是你肚子里的蛔虫
I'm your arms wide open, I'm your pants.
沃德说了算!
Ward's in charge!
如果你想见泰利 我告诉你他在哪儿
If you wanna go see Tyree, I'll give you directions,
但你必须做出选择 因为他是个暴力的男人
but you got to make that choice because he's a violent man.
现在和我待在一起
Now stay with me now,
问题开始变得棘手了
because this is when it gets tricky.
沃德叫了夏洛特
Ward called Charlotte,
告诉她带亚德利到奥蒙德沙滩
and told her to drive Yardley to Ormond Beach.
他想核实希拉里所谓的高尔夫球场的故事
He wanted to verify Hillary's so-called golf course story.
男孩们继续拜访这个泰利叔叔
The boys went on to visit this Uncle Tyree.
兄弟 这太愚蠢了 我们要去哪儿?
Man, this is stupid. Where are we going?
没人住在这外面 没人能住在这外面
No one lives out here. No one could live out here.
你和安妮塔说了你的... 用词?
You talk to Anita about your... choice of words?
这事弄得一团糟
It was fucked up.
我知道
I know.
该死的
Goddamn it.
你确定不用我去看车?
Sure you don't me to watch the car?
该死的! 这东西不管用 伙计
Goddamn it! This stuff ain't working, man.
就像他们喜欢这废物一样
It's like they like this shit.
比水母好多了 我打赌
Better than jellyfish, I bet.
他妈的! 哦 老天!
Fuck! Oh, my God!
小心! 你离它太近了 沃德! 沃德!
Watch it! You're way too close to him. Ward! Ward!
你最好跳过它
You better jump him.
在这好多了 我们不得不蹲低
It's better in here where we have to get lower.
沃德 你陷进去了!
Ward, you're sinking!
这地方就是飘着的
This whole place is just floating.
你曾想过妈妈吗?
You ever think about Mama?
我在想她在哪儿
I wonder where she at.
她在亚利桑那州的图森
She is in Tucson, Arizona.
你交了个女朋友?
You got a girlfriend?
为什么?
Why?
你不记得了 但是妈妈过去常唠叨说 呃...
You don't remember this, but Mom used to go on about, uh...
等你结婚的时候再跟女人亲热 对吧? 嗯...
don't make love to a woman until you get married, right? Mm... hm.
我一直这样做直到我...
I followed that until I was...
哦 他妈的 我们过会儿再聊
Oh, fuck that. We'll talk about it later.
我们走
Let's go.
范・维特尔先生?
Mr. Van Wetter?
下午好 先生
Good afternoon, sir.
我叫沃德・詹森 我为"迈阿密时报"工作
My name is Ward Jansen. I work for "The Miami Times."
我们代表你的侄子希拉里来这儿
We're here on behalf here of your nephew, Hillary.
你丢了一只鞋
You lost a shoe.
你很幸运只遇见了一条蛇
You're lucky it was just the one.
这到处都是蛇
Snakes all around here.
范・维特尔先生 我们需要和你谈谈你的侄子
We need to talk to you about your nephew, Mr. Van Wetter.
有点晚了 不是吗?
Little late for that, isn't it?
他将要被处以死刑
He gonna be strapped to a chair and electrocuted.
呃...
Well...
你来这儿就是告诉我这个?
you come all the way up here just to tell me that?
你本可以不来的
You could've saved yourself a trip.
他告诉我卡尔警长被杀那天
He tells me that he was with you,
他和你在一起
the night Sheriff Call was murdered,
在偷草皮 之后你们就卖了
stealing sod, which you later sold.
没人相信他吧
Let's hope nobody believes him.
偷窃是违法的 不是吗?
Stealing's against the law, ain't it?
现在他还有时间
Now he's still got time.
我不太喜欢你
I don't much care for you.
来我的家...
Come up here in my home...
叫我小偷
and call me a thief.
我来这儿不是为了偷窃一事的 范・维特尔先生
I ain't up here about thieving, Mr. Van Wetter.
我来这儿是关乎一个人的生命能否继续下去...
I'm up here about whether a man's life needs to be taken or not...
因为谋杀卡尔警长一事
for the murder of Sheriff Call.
但如果那晚你和你的侄子在一起
But if you was with your nephew that night,
你承认的话 这对希拉里是生死攸关的
it's vital for Hillary that you admit it.
我觉得他不太喜欢你
I don't think he likes you much.
我也不太喜欢他
I don't like him much either.
冰激凌在哪儿?
Where's the ice cream?
来了
It's coming.
让那个婴儿安静点
Keep that baby quiet.
那个婴儿到底怎么了?
What's wrong with that baby?
好吧 嗯 坐下来
All right, well, sit on it.
是的
Yeah.
你想...?
You want...?
你想来点冰激凌吗?
You want a little ice cream?
你不想吃冰激凌
You don't want to have any ice cream.
你带着这椅子跟我来
You take this chair out here with me.
没道理你呆在那里
No sense you staying over there.
谢谢
Thank you.
小伙计 自己拿把椅子
Little man, get yourself a chair there.
自己拿把椅子
Get yourself a chair.
你和他在一起吗?
Was you with him?
是的
Yeah.
呃 我...
Well, I...
我和他一起
I was with him.
在哪儿?
Where?
高尔夫俱乐部
Golf club.
奥蒙德海滩
Ormond Beach.
偷草皮 再卖...
Stole sod, sold it...
卖给一个公寓开发商
to this one condo developer.
希拉里住在这里的哪儿?
Where's Hillary live from here?
我们直到早上日出才回来
We didn't get back till the morning, sunrise.
他住在那边
He lives that way.
那么你为什么现在告诉我?
So why are you telling me now?
你看起来像是唯一一个相信希拉里是无辜的人
You seem like the only person thinks Hillary's innocent.
不 先生 范・维特尔先生 不是的
No, sir, Mr. Van Wetter. No, sir.
我没那么说过
I didn't say that.
你的伙计...
Your boy...
他在那边紧张不安
he's getting nervous over there.
我们走 我已经和你说完话了
Let's go. I'm done talking to you.
- 你藏了什么?  - 沃德?
- What you hiding?  - Ward?
我对你的问题...
I'm sick...
感到厌恶
of your questions.
嘿尤金?
Eugene?
沃德 记不记得我和夏洛特在一起的第一天? 嗯?
Ward, remember the first day when I was with Charlotte? Yeah?
我们在监狱停了下来
We went and stopped at the prison.
我们没进去 我看见了他
We didn't go in. I saw him.
- 泰利?  - 是的
- Tyree?  - Yeah.
你认为呢? 他们一起编的故事?
What you think? They was getting their stories together?
我不清楚
I don't know.
我告诉你
I'll tell you this.
他们不像看上去那么闷
They ain't as dumb as they look.
哦 该死 伙计
Oh, shit, man.
该死的
Fuck.
搞什么鬼 伙计?
What the fuck, man?
把我留在那该死的酒店?
Leave me at the fucking hotel?
天啊!
Jesus!
依旧在亚德利的房间
In Yardley's room, no less.
该死 伙计 看看你
Fuck, man. Look at you.
你对这起案件着了迷
You're becoming obsessed with this case.
唤醒我吧
Wake me up.
来吧
Come on.
你看起来很糟糕 沃德
You look terrible, Ward.
那些蚊子把你当早餐?
Those mosquitoes eat you for breakfast?
亚德利找到了高尔夫球场
Yardley found the golf course.
- 你找到了高尔夫球场?  - 他穿我的衣服干什么?
- You found the golf course?  - What's he doing in my clothes?
车坏了
The car broke down.
我们不得不走到市里
We had to walk into town,
找个汽车旅馆梳洗一番
stopped by the motel to freshen up.
现在脱下我的衣服
Get out of my clothes now.
好了
Come on.
好了 杰克
Come on, Jack.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
布莱斯小姐 快点 别管了
Miss Bless. Come on, stop it.
嘿杰克!
Jack!
谋杀的那个早上
On the morning of the murder,
奥蒙德海滩高尔夫球场的草地负责人
the grounds superintendent of the Ormond Beach Golf Course,
给警察局打电话
phoned the Police Department,
说他的四块草地
to report that four of his greens,
都在夜里被人偷走了
had been stripped in the night.
- 你和那个负责人谈话了?  - 没
- You talked to the superintendent?  - No.
他死了 不过我找到了另一个人
He died, but I found another guy who remembered,
记得俱乐部给官员打电话
that the club called the governor,
请他宣布那儿是个杂乱无章的地方
to ask him to declare them a disaster area,
这样他们就能得到联邦资金
so they could get federal funds,
来更换草坪了
to replace the greens.
进展的更好了
It gets better.
我也找到了建造者
I found the builder, too,
买了被偷草皮的那个人
the guy who bought the stolen greens.
他记得希拉里和泰利
He remembered Hillary and Tyree.
他们早上六点开卡车露的面
They showed up at 6 AM in a truck.
他看了一眼他们和东西
He took one look at them and what they had,
认为他们是从墓地偷来的
and thought they'd stolen it from a cemetery.
但是当然 无论如何他都不想被牵连进来
But of course, he doesn't want to be connected to this in any way.
他是谁?
And who was he?
嗯 唯一让他和我说话的方法
Well, the only way he'd talk to me,
就是我承诺不说他的名字
is if I promised to keep him anonymous.
快点吧 他叫什么?
Come on now. What's his name?
不 不 不
No, no, no.
我要保密 我给他承诺了
I've got to keep it anonymous. I gave him my word.
他有 呃 他有背景
He's got, well, he's in a position,
为国家工作 所以你懂的
to get some work from the state, so you know.
但是很好 嗯?
But good, huh?
很出色
Outstanding.
你怎么找到他的?
How'd you find him?
建筑执照
Building permits.
该死的建筑执照
Damn building permit.
到摆脱的时候了
Time to get out of Lately.
你和亚德利上床了吗?
Did you sleep with Yardley?
你懂得 像亚德利这种人 你就是...
You know, people like Yardley, you just...
想让他在你身边
got to get him on your side.
你知道我什么意思吗?
You know what I mean?
你因为那样和他上床?
You fucked him for that?
上床是这个世界上最自然的事了 杰克
Fucking a man is the most natural thing in the world, Jack.
是这样的
It is.
我有点喜欢这儿了
I kind of like it out here.
这是个好想法
This was a good idea.
哦!
Oooh!
来吧! 我们跳舞
Come on! Let's dance.
来吧! 不!
Come on! No!
来吧 杰克 来点乐子!
Come on, Jack. Got to have fun!
你想跳舞?
You wanna dance?
是! 我想和你跳舞!
Yeah! I wanna dance with you!
哇! 跳得不错!
Woo! You're good!
我不是在道歉 明白吗?
This is not me apologizing, you dig?
我只是不喜欢看你难过
I just don't like to see you sad.
亚德利把奥蒙德海滩发现的新线索
Yardley told their editor about the new evidence,
告诉了他们的编辑
from Ormond Beach.
这在法律制度中体现公平已经足够了
This was enough to show injustice in the legal system of Lately,
对一个完美的故事来说也足够了
and enough for a good story.
亚德利想离开小镇
Yardley wanted to get out of town,
沃德也知道
and Ward knew it.
地板上的这些花生
All these peanuts on the floor.
蠢猪 一群蠢猪住在这儿
Pigs. Bunch of pigs living around here.
厌烦了这活儿
Sick of this shit.
我找不到妈妈的戒指
I can't find Mama's ring.
哦 一定是个黑鬼半夜
Oh, well, a nigger must have come,
溜进来偷了它
in the middle of the night and stole it.
我很抱歉 安妮塔
I'm sorry, Anita.
我不是想说...
I didn't mean to say...
我不是那意思
I didn't mean to say that.
我真的很抱歉
And I'm really sorry.
你知道吗 小杰克 你必须注意你的言行
You know, Jackie, you got to watch your mouth.
有人会切掉你的屁股 扔在狗屎里
Somebody'll cut your little ass over some shit like that.
你懂吗 孩子?
You understand me, boy?
懂 女士
Yes, ma'am.
你想你的妈妈?
And you miss your mother?
有时会
Sometimes.
她离开你的方式真不仁慈
It's a dis-damn grace the way she left you.
我在这里
And I been here.
好吧 我想 让我们来找戒指吧
Well, let's find this ring, I guess.
不 没关系 我可以找到它
No, that's all right. I can find it.
- 哦  - 抱歉
- Ohhh.  - Sorry.
没关系
All right.
好的
Okay.
- 我真的很抱歉  - 好的
- I'm really sorry.  - Okay.
好了 杰克
All right, Jack.
是什么让这个故事不一样?
What's makes this story any different?
是什么让你的故事和其他人的不一样 约翰?
What makes your story different than the others, John?
到底是什么原因让你现在想结束这个案子?
What makes this case so different that you want to pull the plug now?
事实 还有什么可做的?
The facts. What's left to do?
你已经来这儿一个半月了
You've been up there a month and a half.
我想让你接着干
I want your ass back here.
为了别人救救那废物
Save that shit for someone else.
我对此不满意 你应该也是
I'm not comfortable with it and you shouldn't be either.
我要去奥蒙德海滩找真相
I'm going to Ormond Beach to get the facts.
我想得到一些鳄鱼皮的鞋
I want to get some alligator shoes.
你来操作 这废物会伤了我
You run this article, this shit could hurt me.
我有一些广告商需要考虑
I got advertisers to think of.
广告商? 你想让我为了你的报纸
Advertisers? You want me to be concerned,
考虑一下广告商?
with the advertisers for your newspaper?
沃德 你什么都不知道
Ward, you don't know everything.
他心里有数 爸爸
He knows what he's doing, Pa.
闭嘴! 我没和你说话
Shut up! I'm not talking to you.
他知道怎么编故事
He knows how to get stories,
只是他还不能领会
but what he doesn't fully appreciate,
故事会流传到一个社区里
is that the stories go out into a community.
他们会共鸣
They resonate.
哦 就像被水母蜇的故事?
Oh, like the jellyfish?
像被尿了一身?
Like getting pissed on?
你注意到安妮塔最近表现得很强势吗?
You notice Anita's been acting mighty bossy recently?
- 她向来都那样  - 是啊
- She's always been that way.  - Yeah.
他妈的
Oh, shit.
亲爱的 别管它了 别弄伤自己
Darling, let it go. Don't get yourself hurt.
坐下吧 我叫安妮塔来 安妮塔!
Sit down. I'll get Anita. Anita!
别了 我来收拾吧
Hey, I'll take care of it.
- 安妮塔会收拾的 安妮塔!  - 她有孩子吗? 我不记得了
- Anita will get it. Anita!  - Does she have children? I can't remember.
- 她有两个小孩  - 哦 对了
- She got two kids.  - Oh, yeah.
怎么样 宝贝? 你要去哪?
How you doing, baby doll? Where you going?
去个迎婴派对
A baby shower.
呃 安妮塔 你走之前
Um, Anita, uh, before you go,
来清理下这堆垃圾
could you clean up this mess.
- 都说我会收拾 没事的  - 安妮塔弄就行了
- I said I got it. It's all right.  - Anita's got it.
好吧
I got it.
我收拾
我们要去奥蒙德海滩了
We're going to Ormond Beach.
唉 就直接告诉他们吧
Oh, just come right out and tell them.
我任命了艾伦做主编
I've named Ellen editor-in-chief.
而且...
And...
我们要结婚了
we're getting married.
这是古董
It's an antique.
我知道
I know it is.
这是我妈妈的
This belonged to my mother.
这是我送给她的礼物 还给她 杰克
It was a gift from me. Give it back, Jack.
快还给她
Just give it back to her.
我只有它了
It's all I got.
沃德一直不信亚德利说的话
Ward never believed Yardley's story.
什么建筑执照 匿名消息
Building permits and anonymous sources.
他带上夏洛特和杰克回到了奥蒙德海滩
He took Charlotte and Jack back to Ormond Beach,
想要查个究竟
to get to the bottom of it.
亚德利回了迈阿密的家
Yardley went back home to Miami.
那个建筑商叫什么名字 夏洛特?
What is that builder's name, Charlotte?
什么建筑商?
What builder?
你明知道是什么建筑商
You know exactly what builder.
那个亚德利说买下了草皮的人
The one Yardley says bought the sod.
我不知道 他自己去的
I don't know. He went alone.
我去了理发店
I went to the hairdresser's.
打扮要花很多时间的
Takes a lot to look like this.
夏洛特・布莱斯 你真颓废
Charlotte Bless, you is a mess.
为了把你的老男人救出来
And you'd do anything to get your man,
你会不惜一切... 是吧?
out of jail... wouldn't you?
渴了?
Thirsty, huh?
哦 是的
Oh, yeah.
知道吗 你这么盯着他
You know, you keep staring like that,
会给我们惹麻烦的
we're gonna have a problem.
你上次来究竟发生了什么 夏洛特?
What really happened down there, Charlotte?
你去了理发店之后 出了什么事? 嗯?
After you went to the hairdresser, what happened? Hm?
杰克 能不能让你哥哥把手放开
Jack, would you tell your brother to get his hands off of me?
- 走吧 老兄 咱们去其他地方  - 别紧张啊 弟弟
- Come on, man. Let's go somewhere else.  - Easy, little brother.
放他妈轻松点 孩子
Just fucking relax, boy.
布莱斯小姐什么都不知道 哈?
Miss Bless ain't got no answer, huh?
不可能
I didn't think so.
你哥哥很奇怪
Your brother's acting strange.
他不常喝成这样
Not used to drinking like this.
这还不止
A little more than that.
沃德为什么要这么做?
Why is Ward doing this?
我们明天还要去很多地方呢
We got 50 places to be tomorrow.
这是什么?
What is that?
真漂亮
It's beautiful.
别拒绝
Don't turn it down.
从来没有人给我这样的东西
No one's ever given me something like this before.
如果你想要回去就告诉我 啊?
Well, you just tell me when you want it back, huh?
真美
It's beautiful.
杰克 你想和我上床?
You want me to fuck you, Jack?
那我就让你玩个痛快
Then I'm gonna fuck you any way you want.
杰克
Jack.
杰克!
Jack!
我想要双鳄鱼皮鞋
I want to get some alligator shoes.
啊 杰克
Mmm, Jack.
你打算就任一个女人摆布
You wanted your ass whupped.
你是不是就想这样?
Is that what you wanted?
告诉我你想要什么
Tell me what you want.
你就是头下流的野猪
You're a dirty pig.
我要让你玩个痛快
I'll fuck you any way you want.
不大点的白种猪
Little white pig.
杰克? 杰克! 杰克!
Jack? Jack! Jack!
杰克 醒醒!
Jack, wake up!
沃德的房间出事了
Something's going on in Ward's room.
嘿! 嘿!
Hey! Hey!
住手!
Stop it!
你他妈搞什么?
What the fuck?
救命! 快来救人啊!
Help! We need help!
钥匙他妈的在哪?
Where's the fucking keys?
钥匙究竟他妈的在哪?
Where's the fucking keys, you piece of shit?
他妈的 醒醒!
Motherfucker, wake up!
救命啊!
Help!
钥匙他妈的在哪?
Where are the fucking keys?
沃德 这塑料东西是干嘛的?
Ward, what's the plastic for?
怎么... 怎么会有塑料?
What the... what is the plastic?
没事了 究竟在搞什么?
It's Okay. What the fuck?
我观察了你很多次
I've watched you so often.
你就坐在这 我听说你会敲鼓
You sit here, and I heard that you play a little drum.
- 你都不站起来做点什么  - 没错
- You didn't get up and do anything.  - No.
我听说你唱歌不好听
I heard you couldn't sing,
不过跟我在一起你必须要唱
but with me you are going to sing.
他会好起来的
He's gonna be fine.
你不用睡床尾椅
You don't have to sleep all the way down there.
好吧
All right.
就这一次
Just this once.
电视开着我没办法做
I can't fuck with this TV on.
你看着我说话
Feels kind of awkward to be talking
感觉有点尴尬
while you see this.
不过他们做这个本来就会很尴尬
But it's kind of awkward that they're doing it in the first place.
和杰克同龄的大多数男孩
Most boys Jack's age fall in love,
都会和高中或大学时代的意中人相恋
with their high school or college sweetheart,
但杰克在他妈妈离开后
but Jack never bothered much with girls,
没花过多少心思在女孩身上
after his mama left.
我想你可以说他有被抛弃的情结
I guess you could say he had abandonment issues.
有了夏洛特 就像是有了一个集母亲
With Charlotte, it was like he was getting his mama,
高中情人 和性欲过剩的芭比娃娃
his high school sweetheart, and a oversexed Barbie doll,
于一身的合体
all rolled into one.
不管怎样 我猜你们都看得够多了
Any who, I think y'all seen enough.
我的头发乱死了 别看我
My hair looks like crap. Don't even look at it.
哦 糟糕
Oh, shit.
我要去趟理发店
I got to go to the hairdresser.
头发卷的不对劲
My wig ain't acting right.
我真不明白你他妈
I don't understand what the fuck,
干嘛要和希拉里在一起
you're doing with Hillary.
哦
Oh.
开始了
Here we go.
你不爱他
You don't love him.
- 真的?  - 嗯
- Really?  - Mm-hm.
你怎么知道
You don't know that.
你什么都不懂
You don't know anything.
- 你才20  - 你也没大我多少
- You're 20 years old.  - You're not that much older.
我大你太多了
I'm a lot older.
我们不可能的
It ain't gonna happen.
看着我
Look at me.
我们不现实
It's not practical.
我比谋杀犯还不现实?
I'm not as practical as the murderer?
他是无辜的 杰克 这才是重点
He's not guilty, Jack. That's the point.
- 这不是重点  - 妈的 我就知道你会这样
- That's not the point.  - Fuck this. I knew it would happen.
怎么了?
What?
给你点春光你就...
I give you some ass and suddenly...
听我说... 希拉里没那么坏
Look... Hillary ain't so bad.
我也没那么好
And I'm not so good.
我有另一面
I've got another side.
我有阴暗的一面
I got a fucked-up side,
我的男人不会介意
and it gets along just fine with my man.
你不能把自己分成两面
You can't split yourself into sides.
当然可以 不信问问你哥
Sure, you can. Just ask your brother.
这和沃德有他妈什么关系?
What the fuck does Ward have to do with this?
他也有阴暗的一面 不是因为他是个娈童
He has a dark side and I don't mean him being a fag.
现在这些男人只能互相支持
Now these boys lived for each other.
让杰克伤心的并不是因为沃德是同性恋
Jack wasn't hurt by Ward being a homosexual,
或者是他阴暗的嗜好
or the dark stuff that he was into.
是因为沃德从没告诉过他
He was just hurt that Ward never told him.
- 嗨  - 嘿 你好
- Hi.  - Hey, there.
- 他好多了 很快就没事了  - 很好
- He's doing better. He's gonna be all right.  - Good.
呃 我要走了
So, I gotta go.
走? 你要去哪?
Go where? Where you going?
我要回家
I'm going back home.
你哪也不用去
You don't have to go anywhere.
已经到了这一步了
It's just the way it works.
你犯不着去你不想去的地方
You shouldn't go anywhere you don't want to go.
谁说我不想去?
Who says I don't want to go?
那你干嘛一定要走?
Why do you have to go?
因为我必须走
'Cause I do.
把戒指拿回去
Take this ring back.
亚德利打电话来了
Yardley called the hotel.
你告诉他了?
Did you tell him?
我和他说沃德在沙滩上被人打劫了
I told him Ward got mugged and beaten on the beach.
好吧 那他说什么?
Well, what'd he say?
没什么
Not much.
他只想知道他是不是还活着
Wanted to know if he was gonna make it.
我告诉他情况并不严重
When I told him it wasn't serious,
- 他好像就没什么兴趣了  - 看来他近来帮不了什么忙了
- he kind of just lost interest.  - Well, he's not gonna be much help for a while.
他听起来不需要谁帮忙
Didn't sound like he needed much help.
他不能一个人写这篇报道 夏洛特
He can't go write the story alone, Charlotte.
- 好吧 我们只能等着瞧了  - 他知道的不够
- Well, we'll just have to see.  - He doesn't know enough about it.
这不只是为了一篇报道 杰克
This isn't about a newspaper article, Jack.
这关乎一个人的生命
It's about a person's life.
这才是我们在这的目的 好吗?
That's the whole point we're here, okay?
是为了一个人的生命
So it's about someone's life.
宝贝 别走
Baby, don't go.
你让我已经思维混乱了
You're starting to screw with my head.
听着 你还是个孩子 好吗?
Look, you're a good kid, all right?
你是...
You're...
你... 你有大好前程
You... you got your whole life ahead of you,
还想要我?
and you want me?
杰克去了"迈阿密时报"
Jack went down to "The Miami Times",
试图阻止亚德利发表那篇文章
to try to stop Yardley from publishing the article.
他不想那上面有他哥哥的名字
He didn't want his brother's name on it.
杰克
Jack.
嗨
Hi.
嘿 沃德呢? 你哥哥现在怎样了?
Hey. How's Ward? How's your brother doing?
他从昨天起就一直想和你联系
Been trying to get ahold of you since yesterday.
很好 看来他情况还没那么坏
Good. He's obviously not doing so badly then.
抱歉 我不想被打扰 来吧 坐 坐
Sorry, I didn't want any distractions. Come, sit, sit.
他想看看你都写了什么
He wants to read what you're writing.
我一写完会第一个给他看的 和以前一样
As soon as I'm done, he'll be the first to read it, as always.
妈的! 别跟我讲这些废话!
Damn it! I'm so sick of your shit, man!
这上面也写着他的名字
His name is on that, too.
他想在出版前看一看
He wants to read it before it's published.
好吧? 仅此而已
Okay? That's it.
他只是想提前看一看
He just wants to read it before it's published.
你必须弄清事实
You got to get those facts straight.
你必须弄清全部的事实
You got to get all the facts straight.
你越来越像你哥哥了
You're starting to sound like your brother.
听着 我们有交稿期限
Look, we have a deadline here.
我告诉过你 这就是新闻行业
I've told you, this is the newspaper business.
我们没有时间弄清全部的事实
We don't have time to get all the facts.
我们都知道希拉里被莱特利镇的市民冤枉了
We both know the town of Lately set Hillary up.
- 我们已经够料了  - 这根本他妈不是真相!
- We've got the story.  - It's not the fucking truth!
你想知道什么他妈才是真相?
You want to talk about the motherfucking truth?
你以为我是伦敦人?
You thought I was from London?
如果不把自己装成黑种的007
Ain't no Negro getting a job up in this spot,
一个黑人不可能做到这个位置 明白没?
unless he's a colored motherfucking James Bond, you dig?
有次我喝醉了 把沃德给干了
I got drunk once and let Ward suck my dick.
他被黑人干过 现在他恨死了自己
He got a taste for niggers and now he hates himself.
这就是真相
That's the truth.
回去你哥哥那 小孩
Go back to your brother, boy.
我要赶稿了
I have got a deadline to meet.
你好?
Hello?
让沃德接电话
Put Ward on the phone.
你为什么在文章上署他的名?
Why'd you put his byline on that article?
你凭什么署他的名?
How could you sign his name on that?
告诉他我们把希拉里救出来了
Tell him we got Hillary out.
州长赦免了他
The governor's gonna pardon him.
希拉里被放出来了
Hillary's getting out.
"最近几个月我回想了很多
"I've had some time to think over the past few months,
关于你 我的事
about me, about you.
我还不确定自己想要什么样的生活
I'm not sure I found what I want out of life yet.
我只知道我不想过没有你的日子
All I know is that I don't want to live it without you.
请收回这枚戒指 爱你的 杰克"
Please take this ring back. Love, Jack."
去开门
Get the door.
快他妈的去开门 婊子!
Get the fucking door, bitch!
你他妈是谁?
Who the fuck are you?
- 我是希拉里  - 你他妈想干嘛?
- I'm Hillary.  - What the fuck do you want?
滚出去! 我找夏洛特
Get the fuck out! I'm with Charlotte.
- 那婊子拿了我的...  - 一会儿叫你!
- That bitch took my...  - I'll call you later!
夏洛特 要不要我报警?
Charlotte, you want me to call the police?
你在这儿
There she is.
抱歉 我...
I'm sorry. I... you see,
我本来想给你写信...
I was gonna write you a letter and I was gonna...
不 我不想看你的信 过来
No, I don't need your letters. Come here.
别碰我
Don't touch me.
快过来 别碰你?
Come on here. Don't touch you?
别碰你?
Don't touch you?
好吧
It's okay.
没事的 宝贝
It's all right, baby.
能为我做件事吗?
You want to do something for me?
什么都可以
Anything.
没事的
That's all right.
你在第三封信里说你爱我
You told me you loved me in your third letter.
你爱我吗?
Do you love me?
就这样!
Yes!
你总是这样干女人吗?
You always fuck like this?
上一次也是这样吗?
Like it was the last time?
你觉得我漂亮吗?
Do you think I'm pretty?
你跟那些黑鬼也像这样干吗?
You fuck those niggers like this?
全都插进去了!
Gonna get all inside here!
现在打包你的东西跟我走
Now pack your shit and let's go.
我觉得我不会喜欢住在沼泽里的
I don't think I'm gonna like living in a swamp.
我不想住在沼泽里 我喜欢这儿
I don't want to live in a swamp. I like it here.
这就是他们爱的宣誓
And that was their declaration of love.
然后希拉里带着夏洛特回了沼泽
So Hillary took Charlotte to the swamp.
- 你听说过老亨利吗?  - 没有
- So did you hear about old man Henry?  - No.
他在后院的水边喝醉了
He got drunk in his back yard by the water,
然后鳄鱼过来在他的腿上咬了一大口
and the alligators came out and took a big chunk of his leg.
哈 玩笑而已
Ha. Just joking.
我那个自大的老爹
My daddy rooster, he got jumped,
被他的三个儿子搞垮了
by three of his sons,
所以我还得给他们三个找地方住
so I need to find a home for three of them.
他们现在在我房子里
So he's in my house sitting,
所以我需要... 我知道你那儿有几个女人
so I need... I know you only have hens.
所以我想知道 你愿不愿意照看孩子
That's why I was wondering, you know, if you want to babysit,
你知道的 收养他们三个
you know, adopt three of them for you.
- 不过他们会很好的 因为你那儿有女人  - 不
- But they'd be good though, because you have hens.  - No.
- 你是我唯一的希望了  - 不! 我一个都不想养
- You're my only hope.  - No! I don't want any.
别这样 夏洛特
Come on, Charlotte.
我需要你帮我个忙
I need you to do me a favor.
我需要你帮我寄这封信
I need you to post this thing for me.
上面没有邮票
It ain't got a stamp on it.
- 你今天怎么了?  - 这封信很重要
- What's wrong with you today?  - It's real important.
你能帮我这件事吗?
You think you can do that for me?
你今天都不像你了
You're not acting yourself today.
你的门为什么开着 哼?
Why's your door open, huh?
屋子里一股尿骚味
Smells like piss in here.
沃德 沃德说你可能会过来
Ward Ward said you might show up.
我给他留了纸条
Left him a note.
你身上臭死了
You stink.
我站在这儿都能闻得到
I can smell you from over here.
过来 孩子 过来坐
Come here, boy. Come sit down.
你为什么回去迈阿密?
What you doing back in Miami?
亚德利走了
Yardley's gone.
他放弃了吗?
He quit?
没有
No.
他在纽约
He's in New York.
签了几本书的合约
Signing some book deal.
新新闻界的英雄还是什么鬼东西的 我也不知道
Hero of the new journalism or some kind of shit. I don't know.
老爹让艾伦搬进去了 是吗?
W.W. moved Ellen into the house, huh?
管他的呢
Whatever.
他高兴就行
Whatever makes him happy.
根本就没有什么开发商 杰克
There wasn't no developer, Jack.
好了 我们动身
All right, let's move.
快点 去洗澡 沃德
Come on, go shower, Ward.
我累了
I'm tired.
快去
Come on.
天呐
Jeez.
我总觉得有什么疏漏的地方 杰克
I keep thinking I missed something, Jack.
我好像疏忽了什么地方
Like I missed something I was supposed to see,
触手可及的
that was right in front of me.
比方说什么?
Like what?
那件事的重点
The point of it.
没关系
Doesn't matter.
所有事情都失去控制了
Things got out of hand.
你受伤了
You got hurt,
亚德利签了该死的合同
Yardley got his fucking book deal.
希拉里带夏洛特去了沼泽
Hillary got Charlotte in the swamp.
我的想法... 是... 别浪费水了
The idea... is that... you run the water,
快点进去洗澡
while you're in there with it.
快点 老兄
Come on, man.
嘿
Hey.
要是我们搞不定呢 嗯?
What if we didn't get it right, huh?
那也没差
Makes no difference.
没差吗 杰克?
It makes no difference, Jack?
你根本不知道
You don't know what it feels like,
我现在是什么感受
to get it exactly right now.
只能让事情顺其自然
To get it down just the way it happened.
你准备回去看希拉里
You're going back to see Hillary.
靠 没错
Fuck yeah, I am.
你有她的消息吗?
Do you ever hear from her?
没有
No.
- 布莱斯小姐?  - 没有
- Miss Bless?  - No.
我想知道她现在认为他怎么样 嗯?
I wonder what she thinks of him now, huh?
看不到她坐在门廊上
Can't see her sitting on the porch stoop,
拿着银勺
holding a silver spoon,
等着别人把冰激凌拿过来 你看得到吗?
and waiting for the ice cream carton to come her way, can you?
我调查过了
I dug around.
根本没有证据 没有原因 没有地点
There wasn't no proof, no how, nowhere,
证明他们那天晚上在偷草皮
that they was ever stealing sod that night.
他们想让我闭嘴
They want me to keep my mouth shut.
不想让我讲我的故事 好吧 去他们的
Don't want me to tell my story. Well, fuck them.
我就要讲我的故事 我要写下我的故事
I'm gonna tell my story. I'm gonna write my story,
他们想发表在哪儿就发表在哪儿
and they can publish it wherever the fuck they want to.
妈妈以前总是说你最好...
Yeah, Mama always said you better be...
做正确的最后一名 而不是错误的第一名 孩子
right and be last before you gonna be first and be wrong, boy.
做正确的最后一名 而不是错误的第一名...
Be right and be last before you go gonna be first and be wrong...
是的 我知道!
Yeah, I know!
我听说... 他们说了些有关...
I heard... They said things about...
哦 没错 那都是真的
Oh, yeah. It's all true.
开玩笑了 你应该去见见其他人
Just kidding. You should see the other guy.
微笑 微笑
Smile. Smile.
谢谢
Thank you.
各位注意啦 我们要切蛋糕啦!
Everyone, please. We're cutting the cake!
摄像师哪去了?
Where's the photographer?
嘿 克莱尔 能不能帮我
Hey, Claire, can you hand me,
拿一下那边的盐?
that salt over there?
谢谢
Thank you.
嗨
Hi.
你不应该来这儿
You ain't supposed to be in here.
- 你这样会让我...  - 我给你拿了杯酒
- You gonna get me in...  - I got you a drink.
你知道你老爸已经解雇我了
You know W.W. fired me.
我要跟你老板谈谈
I'm gonna talk to your boss,
告诉他你是我们家的朋友
and tell him you're a friend of the family.
- 不 杰克  - 就这样
- No, Jack.  - Yeah.
我以前做的就只是做饭和给你们兄弟打扫卫生
All I ever did was cook and clean for you boys.
我从来没有过家庭
I wasn't never no family.
不管怎样 出去吧
Anyway, go on back outside.
呃 沃德就在外面 你要见见他吗?
Well, Ward's out there. You gonna come see him?
你想让我被炒鱿鱼吗?
Are you trying to get me fired?
我很想你
I miss you.
我有东西给你 等一下
I got something for you. Wait a minute.
一个月前有人让我把这个拿给你
This came for you about a month ago.
她让他告诉你
She told him to tell.
她跟他说别让你看这个
She told him not to let you see it.
"亲爱的杰克 我不敢相信
"Dear Jack, I can't believe,
我最后还是给你写了这封信
I'm finally writing you this letter,
不知道你能不能拿到这封信
or if it will get to you,
或者你是否会读这封信
or whether you'll even read it.
杰克 我觉得我这次彻底搞砸了
Jack, I think I've really messed up this time.
别误会我的意思
Don't misunderstand me.
希拉里爱我 用他的方式
Hillary loves me, in his way.
只是我不能完全适应这个地方
It's just me that isn't made for this place,
适应这种生活方式
for this lifestyle.
我希望我能去你父亲的婚礼
I hope I can make it to your father's wedding,
那样我就能听到你告诉我 "我早就跟你说过了"
so I can hear you tell me, "I told you so".
好好照顾自己 爱你的 夏洛特"
Take care for now. Sweetly, your Charlotte."
金发妞儿给你的?
Is that from blondie?
谢谢
Thank you.
你的帽子呢?
Where's your hat?
- 哦 我忘了  - 滚出厨房
- Oh, I forgot.  - Get out of the kitchen.
对不起
I'm sorry.
抱歉 我是杰克・詹森 是新郎的儿子
Excuse me. I'm Jack Jansen. I'm the groom's son.
我爸想知道晚饭怎么做了这么久
My father wants to know what exactly is taking dinner so long.
- 马上就好了 先生  - 谢谢
- It'll be ready in a minute, sir.  - Thank you.
把你的头发放进帽子里
Put the hair under the hat.
我可不想在我的吃的里看见你的黑头发
I don't want your black hair in my food.
你可以在我的吃的里放你的黑头发
You can put your black hair in my food.
干杯
Cheers.
拜 安妮塔
Bye, Anita.
拜 杰克
Bye, Jack.
你不会丢下我自己走的 对不对?
You wouldn't leave without me, would you?
把你留在汽车旅馆 我要去个地方
Drop you off at the motel. I'm going somewhere.
介意我问一下你要去哪儿吗?
Mind me asking where you're going afterwards?
去找夏洛特
Going to Charlotte's.
好吧 今晚就去?
Well, it gotta be tonight?
我他妈的要带她离开那个地方
I got to get her the fuck out of there.
我要带她离开那儿!
I got to get her out of there!
夏洛特是按照她自己的意愿决定的
Charlotte's acting on her own free will.
你想让我说什么? 让开
What do you want me to say? Move.
不管怎样我也要去找范・维特尔
I got to go to the Van Wetters' anyway.
明天早上和我一起去
Come with me tomorrow morning.
- 我们现在就去  - 现在不合适
- We're going now.  - It ain't the right time.
- 你他妈的给我让开  - 你喝成这样不能开车
- Get the fuck out my way.  - You ain't driving drunk like this.
你他妈的到底想怎么样 哼?
What the fuck are you gonna do about it, huh?
什么?
What?
夏洛特绝对够劲儿
Charlotte must be a good piece of ass.
- 你看起来就像个海盗  - 我知道
- You look like a pirate.  - I know.
帮我一次 去 "啊哈"
Do this for me one time. Go "Aargh."
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
嘿 你这船开的太奇怪了 哥们
Hey, you're driving all squirrelly, man.
嘿 杰克 坐好 嘿
Hey, Jack, sit on down. Hey.
你确定是这条路吗?
You sure it's this way?
我确定是这条路
I'm sure it's this way.
现在可不是畅饮的好时候 杰克
Ain't a good time to be drinking too much out here, Jack.
是啊 你也就是说说
Yeah, you're one to talk.
你也跟爸爸保证了 对不对?
Keeping your promise to Dad, did you?
不在他的婚礼上喝酒?
Not to drink on his big day?
你遵守了吗?
How you holding up?
我看看你的手 是不是在抖?
Let's see your hands. Are they shaking?
在抖 沃德 哼? 别喝了
They shaking, Ward, huh? Don't drink.
好吧 你怎么像了我最差的地方 杰克?
Well, why do you take after the worst of me, Jack?
因为你是我老哥
'Cause you're my brother.
婚礼 夏洛特?
Wedding party, Charlotte?
我要去婚礼
I'm going to the wedding.
别把事情弄复杂了 我告诉过你...
Don't be difficult. I told you...
我不想让你去
I don't want you to go.
不 我跟你说了 我要去婚礼
No. I told you. I'm going to the wedding.
小心
Watch out.
天哪 闻起来跟屎一样
God, it smells like shit.
是电网 你还好吗?
Electric fence. You all right?
你还好吗?
You all right?
该死的
Goddamn.
我来带路
You let me lead.
我不想跟你吵架
I don't want to quarrel with you.
你是我的小马驹
You're my little pony.
我只想再爬到你身上骑一次
I just want to climb up on you one more time.
我没法相信她住在这儿
I can't believe she'd live here.
夏洛特啊!
Charlotte!
夏洛特?
Charlotte?
夏洛特!
Charlotte!
你想干嘛?
What you want?
她不在
She not here.
她出去了
She gone.
你找我老婆想干嘛?
What is it you want with my wife?
嗯?
Huh?
你找我老婆想干嘛?
What is it you want with my wife?
就想打个招呼
Just wanted to say hello.
快快的打个招呼然后再干一炮吗?
A quick hello and a quick poke while you're at it?
你呢? 你来干嘛 沃德?
How about you? What you up to, Ward?
我知道你来干嘛
I know what you came for.
我知道你想要什么
I got what you want.
她在哪儿?
Where is she?
- 我怎么知道?  - 不见到她我不会走的
- How should I know?  - I'm not leaving until I see her.
她不在这儿 她走了
She not here. She gone.
- 我们走  - 她去哪儿了?
- Let's go.  - Where?
我怎么知道?
How should I know?
昨天晚上她跟我说
Last night she told me,
她要去参加你父亲的婚礼!
she was going to your father's wedding!
你说谎! 我们刚从婚礼上过来!
You're a liar! We just come from there!
所以现在你们应该滚回去 小伙子!
And that's where you should go back to, boy!
他在说谎!
He's lying!
他在说谎
He's lying.
我知道了 回船上去
I got this. Go back to the boat.
她在哪儿? 她在哪儿?
Where is she? Where is she?
别挑衅我 小伙子
Stop provoking me, boy,
照你哥哥说的做!
and do what your brother tells you!
我说了没见到她我不会走!
I said I'm not leaving until I see her!
该死 他杀了她
Goddamn it, he killed her.
他杀了她 沃德
He killed her, Ward.
你杀了她!
You killed her!
你个狗娘养的!
You son of a bitch!
你能干的事儿就是杀了她!
That's all you were good for is killing her!
哼?
Huh?
快跑 杰克!
Run, Jack!
来啊 小伙子 露一手
Come on, boy. Show me.
我会弄死你
I'm gonna fuck you up.
来啊!
Come on!
杰克啊!
Jack!
沃德!
Ward!
沃德啊!
这就是你想要的吗?
Is this what you wanted?
好了
Yeah.
你来这儿的目的达到了
You got what you come for.
小报童
Paperboy.
你要去哪儿 小报童?
Where you going, paperboy?
你跑不掉的
Ain't no way out of this one.
去你妈的!
Fuck you!
希拉里・范・维特尔最终因为
Hillary Van Wetter was tried and convicted,
谋杀了夏洛特・布莱斯和沃德・詹森而被定罪
in the murders of Charlotte Bless and Ward Jansen.
他最后死在佛罗里达州监狱的电椅上
He died in the electric chair at the Florida State Prison.
没人知道到底是谁杀了卡尔警长
Nobody ever found out who murdered Sheriff Call.
我的小杰克在沃德的葬礼上再次见到了他妈妈
My little Jack finally saw his mama again at Ward's funeral.
他成了一个小有名气的作家
He became a writer of some renown.
却再也没有爱上别人
He never did get over his first true love.
（剧终）